# EGOR NAZAROV

+7(952) 643-4809  $\diamond$  Saint-Petersburg, Russia

nazarov.egor2010@yandex.ru \langle linkedin.com/in/nazzrrg \langle t.me/nazzrrg \langle github.com/nazzrrg

### **OBJECTIVE**

Software Engineer with 4 years of experience in back-end development. Looking for part-time Middle+ Golang Backend Developer positions.

My superpower is the ability to balance between "tactical" and "strategical" programming, allowing me to deliver new features without getting bogged down by technical debt.

#### **EDUCATION**

Master of Computer Science, ITMO University, Saint-Petersburg, Russia Bachelor of Information Systems and Technology, ITMO University, Saint-Petersburg, Russia

### **SKILLS**

System Design Microservices, DDD, CQRS and Event Sourcing, GoF design patterns

Tools Docker, Kubernetes, OpenShift, Jenkins, Prometheus, Grafana, ELK-stack, Postman

Soft Skills TDD, BDD, Agile(SCRUM), balancing New Features and Technical Debt

Language Skills Russian - native, English - proficient

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Avito — Software Engineer (E4)

Saint-Petersburg, Russia Aug. 2024 - Present

- Developed a financial mini-app for the largest classified advertisements website in the world (72 mil DAU) using Golang, PostgreSQL, Kafka, JSON-RPC, ELK, Prometheus, Grafana.
- Created a solution for the integration of analytics data to deliver personalized financial product recommendations.
- Helped to design and implement a financial product marketplace on the platform.

### Sber — Senior Software Engineer

Saint-Petersburg, Russia Jan 2024 - Aug. 2024

- Led a major refactor and error handling optimisation, which postponed a complete rewrite of the service by 2+ years.
- Achieved 20% CPU load reduction for one of the microservices through finding an optimal logging solution.
- Developed a microservice-based contact center solution for the largest contact center in Europe (300,000+calls/day) using Golang, PostgreSQL, Kafka, REST, gRPC, OpenShift, ELK.

### Sellematics — Software Engineer

 $Dubai,\ UAE$  Aug 2023 - Jan 2024

- Led the development of a web-fingerprint farming service which led to 75% reduction in fingerprint-related errors.
- Developed a scraper and parser components for the Online Marketplace Analytics Platform using Golang, Redis, MongoDB, Sentry, Prometheus, Grafana and Wireshark.

### Initi — Software Engineer

Moscow, Russia Mar 2022 - Jul 2023

- Pioneered automated testing in the project, which led to 50X reduction of manual testing time for the component and 10% improvement in delivery speed for the whole project.
- Developed a Network and Application Monitoring Solution using a proprietary language, **ClickHouse and Python**.

Diasoft — Junior Software Engineer

Saint-Petersburg, Russia Sep 2021 - Mar 2022

• Developed Apache modules that prepared data for a resource management system using C++ and OracleDB.

# **LEADERSHIP**

• Sep 2021 - May 2022 - freshman mentor. Helped with the adaptation of new students in academic environment. Provided guidance and assistance as well as organised activities aimed at ice-breaking and team-building.